<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Button Example</string>

    <string-array name="nameIndex">

        <item>Mashrafe</item>
        <item>Mushfiq</item>
        <item>Sakib</item>
        <item>Tamim</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="playerDetails">

        <item>He was bought by Kolkata Knight Riders for the 2009 Indian Premier League; although KKR paid US$ 600,000 for Mortaza. Due to his international commitments, Mortaza has infrequently played for Khulna Division in Bangladesh\'s domestic cricket competitions. While he has represented Bangladesh 36 times in Tests and in 100 ODIs between 2001 and 2005 he played only 11 first-class and 9 list A matches for Khulna Division in the same period.\nIn 2012 he joined the Dhaka Gladiators and 2015 from Comilla Victorians in the newly formed Bangladesh Premier League twenty20 competition and captained them to the tournament title and led Comilla Victorians clinched the title of the third 3rd Bangladesh Premier League (BPL) as well as champion of 2017 Bangladesh Premier League fourth time as captain.This time he played for Rangpur Riders. In March 2018, Mortaza took four wickets in four balls bowling for Abahani Limited against Agrani Bank Cricket Club in the 2017–18 Dhaka Premier Division Cricket League. He took his first List A hat-trick and became the first Bangladeshi bowler to take four wickets in four balls in List A cricket. He finished the 2017–18 Dhaka Premier Division Cricket League as the leading wicket-taker of the tournament, with 39 dismissals in 16 matches.</item>
        <item>Before playing for the national team, Rahim played for Bangladesh Under-19s. He represented them in three Youth Tests and 18 Youth One Day Internationals (ODIs) between 2004 and 2006, averaging 31.75 and 36.00 with the bat in the respective formats. Rahim trained at the Bangladesh Institute of Sports. During the 2006 U-19 Cricket World Cup, hosted by Sri Lanka in February, Rahim captained the Bangladesh side which included future international players Shakib Al Hasan and Tamim Iqbal among others. Rahim was one of two players at the tournament with Test-match experience. Under his guidance Bangladesh reached the quarter finals of the tournament.[10] Later that month Rahim was recalled to the senior Test squad for the first time since the England tour in 2005. He was selected as a specialist batsmen, with Khaled Mashud chosen as the wicket-keeper for the series against Sri Lanka.</item>
        <item>Born in Magura, Khulna, Shakib started playing cricket at an early age. According to Prothom Alo sports editor Utpal Shuvro, Shakib was fairly proficient at cricket and was often hired to play for different villages.[11] In one of those matches, Shakib impressed an umpire who arranged for him to practice with the Islampur Para Club, a team in the Magura Cricket League. During the practice session, Shakib batted aggressively and bowled fast, as he usually did, but also chose to experiment with spin bowling which proved to be not so effective. He was picked to play for Islampur and took a wicket with his first ball; it was his first delivery with a proper cricket ball, having previously played with a taped tennis ball. He spent six months training at Bangladesh Krira Shiksha Pratisthan, a government-run sports institute. and in 2004, at the age of 17, was drafted by Khulna to play in the National Domestic League.</item>
        <item>He is currently the highest run-scorer for Bangladesh in international cricket,[6] including Test matches, ODIs and T20 internationals. He is the second Bangladeshi cricketer to score 3,000 runs in Tests and 5,000 runs in ODIs and also the first Bangladeshi cricketer to go past 1,000 runs in T20Is.He has also achived the most centuries for Bangladesh cricket side. Tamim Iqbal is the brother of Nafees Iqbal and the nephew of Akram Khan, who both played Test cricket for Bangladesh. He married Ayesha Siddiqa in June 2013 with a grand ceremony held at Chittagong. Former Prime Minister Khaleda Zia was also present at the event. He had his first son Mohammed Arham Iqbal in 28 February 2016. fter the West Indies series 2011/12, Tamim went to New Zealand to join the Wellington Firebirds. In his month-long spell with the Firebirds, he scored 232 runs, including two half-centuries with an average of 38.66. He came back to Bangladesh in mid January to lead Duronto Rajshahi in second edition of BPL.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
